Guide to the E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection circa 1855-1953
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- People, circa 1855-1953; Series 7
  - Thornton, John S., P101:1353
  - Thornton, John S. and Johny, P101:1354
  - Three people by door of house, circa 1900; P101:0685
  - Three people on steps of a house, circa 1900; P101:0787
  - Three people on steps of a house, circa 1900; P101:0830
  - Three people on steps of a house, P101:0808b
  - Three people playing cards, circa 1900; P101:0683
  - Three people sitting on steps of house, circa 1900; P101:0654
  - Two children in dining room of house, circa 1900; P101:0656
  - Two children next to porch, circa 1900; P101:0680
  - Two unidentified men with rifle and banjo, circa 1900; P101:0457a
  - Two unidentified men with rifle and banjo, circa 1900; P101:0457b
  - Two women in a garden, circa 1900; P101:0652
  - Two women in front yard, circa 1900; P101:0675
  - Two women in garden next to house, circa 1900; P101:0793
  - Two women in hats, Jan. 1, 1899; P101:1248a
  - Two women looking at sheet music, circa 1900; P101:0659
  - Two women sitting on ground, circa 1900; P101:1191
  - Two young girls, circa 1900; P101:0651
  - Two young girls playing, circa 1900; P101:0665
  - Two young girls playing, circa 1900; P101:0666
  - Unidentified man, circa 1930; P101:0779
  - Unidentified woman, P101:1362
  - Unidentified child outside, circa 1910; P101:0813
  - Unidentified boy, circa 1870; P101:0733
  - Unidentified girl, circa 1860; P101:0774
  - Unidentified girl, circa 1865; P101:0776
  - Unidentified girl, circa 1880; P101:0824
  - Unidentified girl, P101:0812
  - Unidentified infant, circa 1870; P101:0724
  - Unidentified infant, circa 1870; P101:0728
  - Unidentified infant at mortuary [?], circa 1865; P101:0734
  - Unidentified man, August 20, 1896; P101:0746
  - Unidentified man, circa 1865; P101:0718
  - Unidentified man, circa 1865; P101:0731
  - Unidentified man, circa 1865; P101:0732
  - Unidentified man, circa 1870; P101:0727
  - Unidentified man, circa 1875; P101:0735
  - Unidentified man, circa 1895; P101:1227
  - Unidentified man, circa 1900; P101:0771
  - Unidentified man, circa 1901; P101:0714
  - Unidentified man, June 26, 1897; P101:1228
  - Unidentified man, P101:1359
  - Unidentified man, P101:1360
  - Unidentified man, P101:1361
  - Unidentified man, P101:1363
  - Unidentified man, P101:1364
  - Unidentified man and woman, circa 1870; P101:0786
  - Unidentified people on steps of building, circa 1900; P101:0510a
  - Unidentified people on steps of building, circa 1900; P101:0510b
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1860; P101:0721
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1860; P101:0722
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1860; P101:0723
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1860; P101:0725
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1860s; P101:0720
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1865; P101:0736
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1865; P101:0737
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1865; P101:0738
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1865; P101:0739
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1870; P101:0740
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1875; P101:0730
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1875; P101:0741
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1880s; P101:0719
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1880s; P101:0729
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1885; P101:0748
    1 photographic print (cabinet portrait)
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1890; P101:1241
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1895; P101:1229
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1895; P101:1239
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1900; P101:0794
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0695
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0696
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0700
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0820
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0821
  - Unidentified woman, circa 1910; P101:0823
  - Unidentified woman, July 1896; P101:0744
  - Unidentified woman, March 1893; P101:1240
  - Unidentified woman wearing a bonnet, circa 1902; P101:0715
  - Unidentified woman wearing a bonnet, circa 1903; P101:0716
  - Unidentified women, circa 1900; P101:0709
  - Unidentified women, circa 1900; P101:0710
  - Unidentified women, circa 1900; P101:0711
  - Unidentified women, circa 1900; P101:0712
  - Unidentified young child, circa 1880; P101:0777
  - Unidentified young girl, circa 1865; P101:0726
  - Unidentified young man, circa 1890; P101:0772
  - Unidentified young woman, circa 1885; P101:0747
  - Unidentified young woman, June 1889; P101:0827a
  - Unidentified young woman, September 10, 1895; P101:0749
  - Wiley, R., circa 1865; P101:0456
  - Williams, Johnie [?], circa 1865; P101:0742
  - Williams, Johnie [?], circa 1865; P101:0743
  - Williams, Jony, P101:1356
  - Williams, Jony [?], P101:1355
  - Wilson Lewis, (mother of), circa 1870; P101:0578a
    1 4x5 glass negative; 1 tintype
  - Wilson Lewis, (mother of), circa 1870; P101:0578b
  - Wilson Lewis, (mother of), circa 1870; P101:0578c
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1875; P101:0423
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1878; P101:0565
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1889; P101:0422
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1890; P101:1230
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1900; P101:0393b
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1905; P101:0390
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1905; P101:0396
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1910; P101:0388a
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1920; P101:0394
  - Wilson, E.E., circa 1950; P101:1311
  - Wilson, E.E. (grandfather of) [?], circa 1900; P101:0645a
  - Wilson, E.E. (grandfather of) [?], circa 1900; P101:0645b
  - Wilson, E.E. (grandfather of) [?], circa 1900; P101:0645c
  - Wilson, E.E. (grandmother of), circa 1900; P101:0847
  - Wilson, E.E. (grandmother of), P101:0848
  - Wilson, E.E. [?] and woman in horse and carriage, P101:0835
  - Wilson, E.E. and others, circa 1950; P101:0566
  - Wilson, E.E. and others laying on lawn, circa 1900; P101:0682
  - Wilson, E.E. in front of house, circa 1900; P101:0663
  - Wilson, E.E. in theatrical production, circa 1900; P101:0579
  - Wilson, E.E. in theatrical production, circa 1900; P101:0580
  - Wilson, E.E. in theatrical production, circa 1900; P101:0581
  - Wilson, E.E., reading, P101:0406
    1 artifact (large metal button)
  - Wilson, E.E., and boy in general store with bottle of Tangle Foot, circa 1900; P101:0804b
  - Wilson, E.E., and father, P101:0407
  - Wilson, E.E., and others under tree, March 1895; P101:0792
  - Wilson, E.E., and T.A. Jones, circa 1900; P101:0412
  - Wilson, E.E., and T.A. Jones, circa 1900; P101:0427
  - Wilson, E.E., and unidentified individual at cemetery, circa 1900; P101:0413
  - Wilson, E.E., and unidentified woman at house on coast, circa 1910; P101:0416
  - Wilson, E.E., and woman, circa 1900; P101:0418
  - Wilson, E.E., as a child, circa 1884; P101:0798
  - Wilson, E.E., eating bread as a young child, circa 1900; P101:0845
  - Wilson, E.E., eating bread as a young child, circa 1910; P101:0846b
  - Wilson, E.E., eating outside of house, P101:0388b
  - Wilson, E.E., in dentist's chair, circa 1905; P101:0389a
  - Wilson, E.E., Leon Louis, and Erma Laurence outside buildings, circa 1890; P101:0409a
  - Wilson, E.E., outside with an axe, P101:0403
  - Wilson, E.E., riding bicycle on plank sidewalk, circa 1900; P101:0431
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting at law office desk, P101:0401
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting in law office, circa 1915; P101:0397b
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting in rocker, reading a magazine, circa 1900; P101:0402
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting on log and holding a small child, circa 1900; P101:1139
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting under a tree, circa 1900; P101:0405
  - Wilson, E.E., standing on steps of coast house, circa 1910; P101:0389b
  - Wilson, E.E., T.A. Jones, and Erna Laurence, circa 1900; P101:0410
  - Wilson, E.E., T.A. Jones, and unidentified individual, circa 1900; P101:0411
  - Wilson, E.E., with axe at coast house, circa 1910; P101:0568
  - Wilson, E.E., with axe at coast house, circa 1910; P101:0569
  - Wilson, E.E., with axe at coast house, circa 1910; P101:0570
  - Wilson, E.E., with Game Commission and staff [?], circa 1945; P101:1309
  - Wilson, E.E., with Game Commission and staff [?], circa 1945; P101:1310
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), circa 1855; P101:0577
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), circa 1900; P101:0460e
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), eating at dining table, circa 1885; P101:0460a
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), sitting on porch steps, circa 1900; P101:0460b
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), sitting on porch steps, circa 1900; P101:0460c
  - Wilson, Lewis (father of), sitting on porch steps, circa 1900; P101:0460d
  - Wilson, Lewis [?] holding small child, circa 1900; P101:0670
  - Wilson, Lewis and Rose, in carriage, circa 1900; P101:0599a
  - Wilson, Lewis and Rose, in carriage, circa 1900; P101:0599b
  - Wilson, Lewis F., circa 1878; P101:0425
  - Wilson, Lewis F., circa 1890; P101:0563
  - Wilson, Lewis F., circa 1920; P101:0417a
  - Wilson, Lewis F., circa 1920; P101:0417b
  - Wilson, Lewis F., P101:0426
  - Wilson, Lewis F. on porch, circa 1910; P101:0484
  - Wilson, Lewis F. on porch, circa 1910; P101:0486
  - Wilson, Lewis F. on porch, circa 1910; P101:0487
  - Wilson, Lewis on bridge at Oak Creek with horse and buggy, circa 1905; P101:0188
  - Wilson, P.G. (wife of), circa 1920; P101:0432
  - Wilson, R.J., circa 1855; P101:0433
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1890; P101:0564a
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1890; P101:0564b
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1890; P101:0564c
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1890; P101:0564d
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1900; P101:0356
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1900; P101:0368
    2 artifacts (large metal buttons)
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1905; P101:0349
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1920Oregon; P101:0827b
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1925; P101:0348
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1925; P101:0357a
    1 photographic print; 1 acetate positive
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1925; P101:0357b
  - Wilson, Rose, circa 1925; P101:0357c
  - Wilson, Rose, P101:0350
  - Wilson, Rose, P101:0351
  - Wilson, Rose, P101:0352
    1 photographic print (halftone)
  - Wilson, Rose, P101:0429
  - Wilson, Rose, P101:0842
  - Wilson, Rose (mother of), circa 1860; P101:0773
  - Wilson, Rose [?] sitting at a dining table, circa 1900; P101:0430
  - Wilson, Rose [?] with two men and a dog, circa 1910; P101:0789
  - Wilson, Rose [?] with two men and a dog, circa 1910; P101:0834
  - Wilson, Rose and Lewis on steps of home, circa 1915; P101:0382
  - Wilson, Rose and Lewis, at coast house, circa 1900; P101:0576a
  - Wilson, Rose and Lewis, at coast house, circa 1900; P101:0576b
  - Wilson, Rose in bonnet with matching print dress, circa 1900; P101:0374
  - Wilson, Rose next to rose bush, P101:0631
  - Wilson, Rose with groups on steps of house, circa 1900; P101:0373
  - Wilson, Rose, among shrubs, circa 1905; P101:0367a
  - Wilson, Rose, among shrubs, circa 1905; P101:0367b
  - Wilson, Rose, among shrubs, circa 1905; P101:0367c
  - Wilson, Rose, and others on porch, circa 1905; P101:0362
  - Wilson, Rose, and others on porch, P101:0365
  - Wilson, Rose, and unidentified woman sitting on a bench surrounded by ivy trellis, circa 1900; P101:0428
  - Wilson, Rose, by fish pool, P101:0634
  - Wilson, Rose, in kitchen, circa 1905; P101:0355
  - Wilson, Rose, in kitchen, circa 1905; P101:0359
  - Wilson, Rose, in kitchen, circa 1905; P101:0366
  - Wilson, Rose, in wheelbarrow with luggage [?], circa 1900; P101:1280
  - Wilson, Rose, on Oak Creek bridge, circa 1900; P101:0609
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting in parlor of house, circa 1900; P101:0369
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting in wicker rocker, circa 1900; P101:0371
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting in wicker rocker, circa 1900; P101:0372
  - Wilson, rose, sitting in wicker rocker, circa 1900; P101:0377a
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on porch steps, circa 1905; P101:0360
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on porch, P101:0363
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on porch with dog, circa 1900; P101:0370
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on steps of home, circa 1905; P101:0353
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on steps of home, circa 1905; P101:0354
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on steps of home, circa 1905; P101:0358
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on steps of home with Lewis Wilson, circa 1915; P101:0381
  - Wilson, Rose, sitting on steps with another woman, circa 1900; P101:0379a
  - Wilson, Rose, standing behind vining bush, circa 1900; P101:0375
  - Wilson, Rose, standing in backyard, circa 1905; P101:0361
  - Wilson, Rose, standing in front of vining bush, circa 1900; P101:0377b
  - Wilson, Rose, with dog on Oak Creek bridge, circa 1900; P101:0376a
  - Wilson, Rose, with dog on Oak Creek bridge, circa 1900; P101:0376b
  - Wilson, Rose, with family on porch of a house at the coast, circa 1910; P101:0380
  - Wilson, Rose,on porch with sister, P101:0364
  - Wilson, Lewis, sitting on porch, circa 1900; P101:0645d
  - Woman and child, circa 1895; P101:1243
  - Woman and young girl, P101:0828
  - Woman from back, P101:0811
  - Woman holding baby, circa 1900; P101:0648
  - Woman in wedding dress, circa 1900; P101:0782
  - Woman on steps of house, circa 1910; P101:0708
  - Woman sitting in chair next to window, circa 1900; P101:0668
  - Woman sitting on porch steps, circa 1910; P101:0705
  - Woman sitting on porch steps, crocheting, circa 1910; P101:0814
  - Woman standing next to barn wall, circa 1910; P101:0825
  - Woman standing next to camera [?], circa 1910; P101:1207
  - Woman standing on bridge at Oak Creek, circa 1900; P101:0186
  - Women on porch of home, circa 1900; P101:0676
  - Women on porch of home, circa 1900; P101:0677
  - Wright, George, circa 1910; P101:0466
  - Wright, George (wife of), circa 1905; P101:0470
  - Wyatt, Cynthia, P101:1357
  - Young girl and baby, circa 1905; P101:1244
  - Young girl and carriage with baby, circa 1887; P101:0643
  - Young man in E.E. Wilson's law office, circa 1895; P101:1236
  - Young man in front of automobile, circa 1915; P101:1276
- Souvenir Views of British Columbia and Alaska, 1915; Series 8
  Series 8 is comprised of a set of 10 commercial souvenir photographs with views of landmarks in British Columbia and Alaska. Wilson may have purchased these photographs during a trip to the area.
  - Aerial view of Ocean Falls, circa 1915; P101:0211
  - Aerial view of the Powell River Pulp Plant, circa 1915; P101:0216
  - Anyox mills, circa 1915; P101:0212
  - Entrance to Queen Charlotte Sound, circa 1915; P101:0208
  - Greenville Channel, near the Skeen River, circa 1915; P101:0215
  - Liner "Prince George" near Skagway, circa 1915; P101:0213
  - Point Atkinson Lighthouse, near Vancouver, circa 1915; P101:0214
  - Prince Rupert, looking toward Tucks Inlet, circa 1915; P101:0210
  - Rosseau Range, Portland Canal, circa 1915; P101:0217
  - Totem poles, Albert Bay, circa 1915; P101:0209